<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Game on Alon Talmi&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://phoder1.github.io/categories/game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Game on Alon Talmi&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 08:06:25 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://phoder1.github.io/categories/game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Age Of The Guardians</title>
      <link>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/academic/ageoftheguardians/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/academic/ageoftheguardians/</guid>
      <description>---  Feel free to download the game&amp;rsquo;s rule book and character sheet:
 Rule Book Character Sheet   About the game Age Of The Guardians is Tabletop RPG game about Aulara, a young, mystical and vibrant world who’s still recovering from the rise and fall of the gods. It&amp;rsquo;s played by 2+ players, every game is an adventure with one player taking the role of the game master, while the rest create and become unique characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-Pirate</title>
      <link>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/academic/co-pirate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/academic/co-pirate/</guid>
      <description>---  About the game Co-Pirate is a multiplayer 2v2 pirates battle game all about sink-or-be-sunk, each team need to shoot cannon balls at the enemy team and fix holes in her own ship before it sinks. Co-Pirate was the final project in my Multiplayer course, we used Photon Engine to make it.
My part in the project I was one of 3 developers working on the project, I was mainly in charge of the in-game mechanics and some multiplayer features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paws Of Fury</title>
      <link>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/academic/pawsoffury/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/academic/pawsoffury/</guid>
      <description>---  About the game Paws Of Fury is a 2.5D mobile battle arena game, Where real-time strategy meets puzzle. The game combines elements from tower defense, collectible card games and merging.
Paws Of Fury was made as my Production course project in my 2nd year.
My part in the project I was the solo developer of the game, and I built and designed all of the systems of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phantom Beasts: Redemption</title>
      <link>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/professional/phantombeasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/professional/phantombeasts/</guid>
      <description>Phantom Beasts is a very story-rich, side-scrolling, action game in 2.5D.
It mixes the fast-paced combat of the ‘shoot’em up’ genre with the precise movement of the platformer genre.
In Phantom Beasts you can have multiple weapon as well as multiple abilities given to you by your teammate phantoms, which creates a very varied and interesting gameplay.
My part in the project I joined ReadySteady Games in my 2nd year of my bachelor degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spacetaurant</title>
      <link>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/professional/spacetaurant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/professional/spacetaurant/</guid>
      <description>---  
Spacetaurant is a mobile, casual idle game combining management and gathering.
The game is about running a futuristic and cute restaurant on a intergalactic highway.
You play as the owner of the restaurant, who collects and grows ingredients to make sure all your customers leave your restaurant satisfied and hopefully leave you a good review.
Spacetaurant was part of R2G - a game development acceleration program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survive The Void</title>
      <link>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/academic/survivethevoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/academic/survivethevoid/</guid>
      <description>---    About the game Survive The Void is a 2D, randomly generated, isometric sandbox game in a fantastic alien space, inspired by Minecraft&amp;rsquo;s SkyBlock mod.
Survive The Void was the Unity project in Advanced Unity course I did in my 2nd year of my game development bachelor degree.
My part in the project Survive The Void was a team of 5 developers, which I was both lead developer and producer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summoners Royale</title>
      <link>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/professional/summonersroyale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phoder1.github.io/posts/professional/summonersroyale/</guid>
      <description>---  Upcoming :)</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
